Guide to the Dan Nimrod papers, 1938-2002 MS2192
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Publications, 1959-2002; MS2192 Series 8; 5 Linear feet
  This series contains publications by Dan Nimrod and Dawn Publishing Company. It contains books, bound copies, and stapled circular correspondence. It includes some of Nimrod's early educational manuals. The material dates from 1959-2002, but the bulk is from 1977-2002. It is sorted in chronological order. Most of the material relates to the Arab-Israeli conflict, but includes other issues such as apartheid in South Africa and the Nicaraguan civil war.
  - Pesach anthology, 04/1959 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Lag Ba-omer anthology, 05/26/1959 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Kol Hagshama closing edition, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - The Integrity of Palestine: Jews and Arabs - Israel and Jordan, 08/1975-09/1975 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Quebec Parties need a united front, 08/10/1977 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Liberals' rejection of common front ignores the lesson of Likud win in Israel, 09/19/1977 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Common front idea 'sound', 09/15/1977 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Quebec Tribune would pave the way for English-French communication, 10/20/1977 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Sinai claims may hurt Israeli security, 02/14/1978 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - 'Liberated vs. occupied' is territorial dilemma, 02/17/1978 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - The Palestine Problem: It's all in a name, 03/13/1978 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - The other side: Israelis a wise U.S. investment, 03/28/1978 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Sadat's Strategy, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Excerpts, 01/14/1979 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Alternative Positions: The Cardinal Principle, 02/1979-03/1979 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Jewish rights vs. Arab claims, 10/1980 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - The Canadian Jewish Herald - Interim Peace Edition, 10/1980 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Testimony and Warning - Centennial Edition - Reflections on a pattern of behaviour, 11/1980 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - On being trapped with the view of the past: The media's hypocrisy, Double Standard, 06/03/1981 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - The Jerusalem Cathedra: The separation of Trans-Jordan from Palestine, 06/03/1981 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Statements: Main points of a statement at the United Nations General Assembly on the question of Palestine, 12/02/1981 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Lucow, Maurice - Editor Canadian Jewish News, 12/21/1981 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - American Middle East Foreign Policy, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - L'autodetermination pour les Palestiniens, 05/01/1982 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Jordan is Palestine - [Advertisement], 04/1982-05/1982 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Jordan is Arab Palestine - Compare Notes #1 - Nedava, Yosef, 06/1982 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Tribute to Irving Taitel-Hatan Mitzvah 1982, 06/19/1982 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - The Palestinian Features of Jordan - Compare Notes #2 - Nisan, Mordechai, 07/1982 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - First International Conference of "Jordan is Palestine" - The Position of the Canadian Delegation, 07/20/1983 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Resume of the relevant deliberations and resolutions on crucial issues confronting the Jordan is Palestine Campaign, 08/17/1983 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Where's Palestine?, 09/02/1982 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Jordan as the Palestinian State, 10/20/1982 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - The Arcand Affair Revisited, 10/01/1982 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - That "brave" U.S. Marine, 02/17/1983 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Britain still fighting the Irgun - The British-Zionist Conflict, 03/04/1983 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - But is it Palestine?, 03/18/1983 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Memorandum for the Secretary of Defense, 06/29/1967 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - What the Joint Chiefs saw as 'Defensible borders', 03/09/1983 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - The Joint Chiefs on Israel's borders, 04/15/1983 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Another clash with Britain, 03/16/1983 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Jewish rights vs. Arab claims - a new alternative in the peace process of the Arab-Israeli conflict - part three, 03/24/1983 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Hussein holds the key, 04/14/1983 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Is Jordan really Palestine?, 06/17/1983 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Palestinian Homelands, 06/24/1983 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Partition semantics, 06/28/1983 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Partitioning Palestine, 06/30/1983 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Is Jordan Palestine?, 07/01/1983 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Palestine's Rise and Fall, 07/08/1983 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Has Likud lost the will to govern?, 09/27/1983 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Where it all went wrong - economic mess has labor roots, 10/13/1983 (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Anderson, Sarah Ms., Public Affairs Director, Consulate General of the U.S., 11/19/1983 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Lucy Dawidowicz and the "Holocaust Industry", 12/01/1983 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Peace Now: Blueprint for National Suicide - Compare Notes #3 - Nimrod, Dan, 03/1984 (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - The People Versus Peace Now, Appendix V - Intellectuals and the Prospect of War, 04/1984 (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Carter, Mondale and the politics of compassion - Morrisey, Will, 07/1984 (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - The Fateful Triangle - Book Reviews, 06/16/1984-07/14/1984 (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - Moffitt, Larry R., Executive Director World Media Conference, 09/21/1984 (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - Government 'access' - myth or reality?, 12/06/1984 (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - No solution to the Arab-Palestinian Problem - Compare Notes #4 - Katz, Shmuel, 03/1985 (Box 14, Folder 59)
  - The axis of antisemitism - Compare Notes #5 - Carpi, Daniel, 04/1985 (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - Toward a new American Middle East policy - Compare Notes #6 - Goldman, Peter E., 05/1985 (Box 14, Folder 61)
  - The case of Israel's Jewish underground - Compare Notes #7 - Eidelberg, Paul, 06/1985 (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - Physical insecurity motivated 'Israel 27', 08/08/1985 (Box 14, Folder 63)
  - A 1985 update on Arab anti-semitism (Box 14, Folder 64)
  - Safety first: The best safety device is a new American Middle East policy (Box 14, Folder 65)
  - This call is for you: Dig into the facts...while you consider this, 05/21/1985 (Box 14, Folder 66)
  - The Cdn Jewish Herald "To set the record straight": Peace Now-undermines the Israeli Govn't, 01/01/1985 (Box 14, Folder 67)
  - Journalistic ethics and the unification church: A dwn report on a multinational communications org., 01/01/1985 (Box 14, Folder 68)
  - How are the mighty fallen, 02/06/1985 (Box 14, Folder 69)
  - Jewish rights vs. Arab claims: Part 2 1920-1955, 03/01/1985 (Box 14, Folder 70)
  - Pipe dreams of peace, 03/18/1985 (Box 14, Folder 71)
  - Profile of Yitzhaq Ben-Ami, Zichrono Livracha, 04/10/1985 (Box 14, Folder 72)
  - The peace maker's illusion, 05/28/1985 (Box 14, Folder 73)
  - The common denominator in American Middle East policy, 05/03/1985 (Box 14, Folder 74)
  - Warhorse' records tragic/heroic years, 05/03/1985 (Box 14, Folder 75)
  - Petition: Please ... President Herzog free the Jewish underground, 07/01/1985 (Box 14, Folder 76)
  - The role of Arab political culture and history in the conflict with Israel - Compare Notes #8 - Soloway, Arnold M., 08/1985 (Box 14, Folder 77)
  - The Hon. Terence Prittle: Reflections on a personal encounter (extract from a letter to an English friend), 09/02/1985 (Box 14, Folder 78)
  - The peace process 1985 - Political analysis, policy outline: Propositions for resolutions (3rd printing), 09/27/1985 (Box 14, Folder 79)
  - From the bookshelf: A timely expose', 10/01/1985 (Box 14, Folder 80)
  - Peace Now: Blueprint for National Suicide (reviewed), 11/01/1985 (Box 14, Folder 81)
  - The first ten years of UN stand on Zionism, 06/11/1985 (Box 14, Folder 82)
  - The 'PLO' terrorism and national security, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 83)
  - Political digest: Views of the Middle East conflict rarely seen in the media, 01/1985 (Box 14, Folder 84)
  - PLO objectives/aims & means, 11/05/1985 (Box 14, Folder 85)
  - Abba Eban reconsidered, 12/1985 (Box 14, Folder 86)
  - 1986 update of "Sadat's Strategy" (Box 14, Folder 87)
  - Petition: Has Britain surrendered to international terrorism?, 01/27/1986 (Box 14, Folder 88)
  - The London declaration, 01/01/1986 (Box 14, Folder 89)
  - Assessing Israel's chances for peace, 02/03/1986 (Box 14, Folder 90)
  - Zionism: Success story of Israel, 10/02/1986 (Box 14, Folder 91)
  - Book review: Eidelberg urges forceful deterrence of terrorists, 03/03/1986 (Box 14, Folder 92)
  - The Kahane phenomena and Jewish 'Jihad', 04/03/1986 (Box 14, Folder 93)
  - Dear Mr. Kaplan: "'Nazi, racist' are well-worn epithets", 05/29/1986 (Box 14, Folder 94)
  - Dear Mr. Kaplan: "'Perverted thinking' mars the defense of Kahane", 05/14/1986 (Box 14, Folder 95)
  - History in the making Dawn collector's library "to set the record straight", 06/01/1986 (Box 14, Folder 96)
  - Linda Chavez U.S. Senate: Maryland candidate announces opposition to Saudi arms sale, 06/05/1986 (Box 14, Folder 97)
  - (Translation of article in "Yidiot Acharonot" on May 28, 1986): The British perpetrated the pogrom in Hebron, 06/12/1986 (Box 14, Folder 98)
  - No peace for Peres - he's aging well, 07/29/1986 (Box 14, Folder 99)
  - Polemical Documents Series: the Jewish "Jihad" against Kahane, 08/01/1986 (Box 14, Folder 100)
  - You deserve a factual look at... "The Palestinian Problem": Is it the cause for unrest in the Middle East?, 08/11/1986 (Box 14, Folder 101)
  - Open letter to "Viewpoints" Canada, 08/20/1986 (Box 14, Folder 102)
  - Dan Nimrod: The one-man Zionist Hasbara campaign, 08/01/1986 (Box 14, Folder 103)
  - State-sponsored terrorism and the threat to international security - Compare Notes #9 - Causa International, 09/1986 (Box 14, Folder 104)
  - Onward Jewish settlers: A short history of Gush Emunim, 09/10/1986 (Box 14, Folder 105)
  - Why Pretoria fears one-man, one-vote, 09/19/1986 (Box 14, Folder 106)
  - "It thinks inside me...": Fassbinder, Germans & Jews, 09/30/1986 (Box 14, Folder 107)
  - Inside view: Lavi expresses U.S.-Israeli partnership: Strategic cooperation between nations has begun, at long last, 09/03/1986 (Box 14, Folder 108)
  - Dear Mordechai, 09/29/1986 (Box 14, Folder 109)
  - Letter from Professor J. Nedava: Dear Dan Nimrod, 09/24/1986 (Box 14, Folder 110)
  - The PLO: antithesis of national liberation - Compare Notes #10 - Nisan, Mordechai, 10/1986 (Box 14, Folder 111)
  - The Canadian Jewish Herald - Gush-Emunim Edition - Dawn Collector's Library, 11/1986 (Box 14, Folder 112)
  - Dear Mr. Nimrod, 11/21/1986 (Box 14, Folder 113)
  - Shamir's no.1 problem, 11/1986 (Box 14, Folder 114)
  - Communism in Nicaragua: what is to be done? - Compare Notes #11 - Muravchik, Joshua, 12/1986 (Box 14, Folder 115)
  - Terrorism by the Israelis, 12/1986 (Box 14, Folder 116)
  - The forgotten killer can't duck the blame: Leading Palestinian figure floats idea for an international peace conference without any pre-condition, 01/1987 (Box 14, Folder 117)
  - An encounter with the homeland after a quarter of a century: A tribute to Israel's 38th independence day (Part one), 1986 (Box 14, Folder 118)
  - Why Kahane should not be barred from entering Canada, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 119)
  - Viewpoint: Temple Mount banned to access by Jews, 01/1987 (Box 14, Folder 120)
  - What might bug you in 1987?, 02/1987 (Box 14, Folder 121)
  - The Temple, 02/1987 (Box 14, Folder 122)
  - The Western Wall, 04/1987 (Box 14, Folder 123)
  - Dear Luis, 05/1987 (Box 14, Folder 124)
  - Dear Elyakim, 07/07/1987 (Box 14, Folder 125)
  - The Hadassah Marcus Dossier (The Jewish People versus the Jewish Agency): A case history..., 06/10/1987 (Box 14, Folder 126)
  - Petition to the Jewish agency, the UJA, the UIA, the JNF and the WZO, 06/1987 (Box 14, Folder 127)
  - Dear Dan, 07/06/1987 (Box 14, Folder 128)
  - Dear Mr. Nimrod, 07/23/1987 (Box 14, Folder 129)
  - Defund the Jewish Agency, 07/01/1987 (Box 14, Folder 130)
  - Dear Elyakim, 07/21/1987 (Box 14, Folder 131)
  - The shock of withdrawal... The State of Israel from the Land of Israel - Compare Notes #12 - Ha'etzni, Elyakim, 08/1987 (Box 14, Folder 132)
  - Dear Dan, 08/07/1987 (Box 14, Folder 133)
  - Dear Meir, 08/15/1987 (Box 14, Folder 134)
  - Dear Mr. Horwin, 08/11/1987 (Box 14, Folder 135)
  - Reflections on Lamentations, 08/04/1987 (Box 14, Folder 136)
  - Dear Dan, 07/22/1987 (Box 14, Folder 137)
  - The Arab Palestine Scenario, 08/01/1987 (Box 14, Folder 138)
  - Seventy years of Evil: Soviet crimes from Lenin to Gorbachev, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 139)
  - The United Nations, Zionism and Racism - Compare Notes #13 - Curtis, Michael, 09/1987 (Box 14, Folder 140)
  - Dear Sir, 09/09/1987 (Box 14, Folder 141)
  - News item concerning the Temple Mount, 08/01/1987 (Box 14, Folder 142)
  - Dear Dan, 08/27/1987 (Box 14, Folder 143)
  - Dear Friend, 09/29/1987 (Box 14, Folder 144)
  - [Attached to this sheet are three pieces of information that I consider extremely important], 09/01/1987 (Box 14, Folder 145)
  - The UJA and the Liberated Territories, 09/04/1987 (Box 14, Folder 146)
  - Dear Mr. Nimrod, 09/04/1987 (Box 14, Folder 147)
  - Dear Dan, 09/03/1987 (Box 14, Folder 148)
  - The Camp David Autonomy Plan, a scenario for the ruin of the land of Israel, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 149)
  - Rapid Jordanisation in the Land of Israel, 09/07/1987 (Box 14, Folder 150)
  - Desperately needed: No support for Israelis beyond the 'Green Line', 09/01/1987 (Box 14, Folder 151)
  - Terrorism in Sri Lanka: Nationalist or Marxist? - Compare Notes #14 - Tremayne, Penelope & Geldard, Ian, 10/1987 (Box 14, Folder 152)
  - Startling, dangerous policy which must be reversed, 10/16/1987 (Box 14, Folder 153)
  - Dear Mr. Spen, 10/20/1987 (Box 14, Folder 154)
  - Dear Shraga, 10/12/1987 (Box 14, Folder 155)
  - Top Priority, 11/13/1987 (Box 14, Folder 156)
  - Dear Joseph, 10/19/1987 (Box 14, Folder 157)
  - Dear Gary, 11/06/1987 (Box 14, Folder 158)
  - Dear Howard, 11/11/1987 (Box 14, Folder 159)
  - Seventy years of Evil: Soviet crimes from Lenin to Gorbachev, 11/1987 (Box 14, Folder 160)
  - Rabin blames Jews for disturbances on the Temple Mount, favours a religious status quo at holy places, 11/1987 (Box 14, Folder 161)
  - Toronto Zionist Council: Statement, 10/05/1987 (Box 14, Folder 162)
  - Dear Friend, 11/02/1987 (Box 14, Folder 163)
  - Dear Mr. Spen, 11/02/1987 (Box 14, Folder 164)
  - Dear Dan, 11/10/1987 (Box 14, Folder 165)
  - Re: The matter of UJA and JNF funding across the Green Line, 11/18/1987 (Box 14, Folder 166)
  - Certificate of Consolidation of The Jewish Agency for Israel, Inc. and United Israel Appeal, Inc. into The Jewish Agency for Israel, Inc. under the name United Israel Appeal, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 167)
  - "Shocking revelation" threatens philanthropy in West Bank, 11/1987 (Box 14, Folder 168)
  - UJA funding controversy may explode at Zionist Congress, 11/1987 (Box 14, Folder 169)
  - An attempt to squash the UN Zionism=Racism Resolution, 11/1987 (Box 14, Folder 170)
  - We must redeem the Temple Mount, 11/1987 (Box 14, Folder 171)
  - Middle East and Mediterranean Outlook: Memo, 12/1987 (Box 14, Folder 172)
  - Ha'etzni/Abelson: Safety Originals, 12/27/1987 (Box 14, Folder 173)
  - Dear Mr. Leiman, 12/08/1987 (Box 14, Folder 174)
  - Dear Dan, 12/10/1987 (Box 14, Folder 175)
  - The climate of fear: A symposium, 12/24/1987 (Box 14, Folder 176)
  - Letter from Jerusalem: How not to be a Zionist, 12/1987 (Box 14, Folder 177)
  - Letters: Thoughts of a Palestinian Jew, 12/14/1987 (Box 14, Folder 178)
  - Ha'etzni, Elyakim, 12/27/1987 (Box 14, Folder 179)
  - Nimrod, Dan, 12/29/1987 (Box 14, Folder 180)
  - Israel at the Bar, 01/01/1988 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Letters: Israel - Homeland of the Jews, 01/18/1988 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Dear Dan, 01/11/1988 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Dear Dan, 01/06/1988 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Dear Julian, 01/29/1988 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Israel in the stone age, 02/1988 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - UIA: Prudent Responsibility, 02/1988 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - UJA & JNF won't aid Jews of Gaza & West Bank: State Dept. denies there's a ban beyond the green line, 02/1988 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Dear Stanley, 02/15/1988 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Dear Dan, 02/09/1988 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Dear Dan, 03/27/1988 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Dear Ambassador Arad, 03/1988 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Self-defense strictly forbidden, 03/29/1988 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Case histories: The left hand rejects what the right hand is doing (Histories on JNF's abdication from Zionist Goals), 04/1988 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Names in the news: To Whom it May Concern, 04/01/1988 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Advocates reveal Anti-Semitic bias, 05/06/1988 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Dear Dan, 06/06/1988 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Polemical documents series, June 30th, 1988: Off the record confidentially speaking, 06/30/1988 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Dear Mr. Sontag, 08/14/1988 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Dear Monroe, 09/01/1988 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - 14- Star Members of the HIT PARADE within the divided nationalist..., 08/1988 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Report in 3 parts of the Leonard Horwin personal fact finding tour to Israel. Part One: Report on Moleded, 10/1988 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Report in 3 parts of the Leonard Horwin personal fact finding tour to Israel, Part Two: Presentation of the International Christian Embassy Jerusalem, 11/1988 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Report in 3 parts of the Leonard Horwin personal fact finding tour to Israel. Part Three: Personal glimpses, viewpoints... - January-December, 1988, 12/1988 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Which Palestine?, 09/01/1988 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - International meeting: No panacea, 03/01/1988 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Polemical Documents Series: Meir Kahane, the litmus test of democracy in Israel, 09/01/1988 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Dear Mr. Ben-Dor, 10/11/1988 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Soviet policy: Beyond containment, 10/01/1988 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Israel shouldn't take link with U.S. for granted: Washington has 3 other allies in region and does not need an expansionary fourth, 10/01/1988 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Retain the Israel asset: 100 retired U.S. generals agree that Israel must retain the Jordan River at its defense border, 10/12/1988 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Lest we forget what is to be done? A solution to the Middle East impasse, 10/06/1988 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - You deserve to know the facts about... Jordan. Is it or is not Palestine?, 10/01/1988 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - To Whom it May Concern, 10/14/1988 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - "Thank you for your communication of November 4...", 11/23/1988 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Dear Dan, 11/27/1988 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Dear Sol, 11/09/1988 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Dear Dan, 11/11/1988 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Dear Dan, 11/11/1988 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Dear Mr. Nimrod, 12/05/1988 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Canadiana: Protester holds sign as he walks in front of Hydro-Quebec building yesterday, 12/18/1988 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - To the immediate attention of members of the Knesset and fellow Jews everywhere, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Likud on a historical threshold, 01/01/1989 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Dear Alex, 01/26/1989 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Dear Dan, 01/15/1989 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Timely warning, 01/01/1989 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - EEC ministers meet Arafat, 02/01/1989 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Dear Dan, 02/03/1989 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Israel: A lamentation from the future, 03/21/1989 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Letters from readers [re: "Israel: A lamentation from the future"], 07/01/1989 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Dear Ms. Magid, 03/17/1989 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Dear Bob, 03/07/1989 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Dear Dan, 03/30/1989 (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Dear Ms. Magid, 03/31/1989 (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Dear Dr. Hecht, 04/23/1989 (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Sparks fly as Rabin admits that the army has refrained from going all-out against rioters, 05/1989 (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Memo from Dan Nimrod re: Hazit Eretz Yisrael, 05/19/1989 (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - Dear Alex, 05/16/1989 (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - Dear Jay, 06/07/1989 (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - From: Dan Nimrod, Canada - To: Alex Kans, Israel, 07/05/1989 (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - Dear Leonard, 09/28/1989-10/28/1989 (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - Dear Leonard, 09/28/1989 (Box 15, Folder 62)
  - A people without a land?, 10/30/1989 (Box 15, Folder 63)
  - Auschwitz 1989: The second encounter, 10/01/1989 (Box 15, Folder 64)
  - The joke of the century: Territory for peace, 10/01/1989 (Box 15, Folder 65)
  - Israel isn't suicidal, 10/22/1989 (Box 15, Folder 66)
  - Israel must keep land, Balfour declares, 11/10/1989 (Box 15, Folder 67)
  - Dear Mr. Sontag, 11/12/1989 (Box 15, Folder 68)
  - Dear Elyakim, 11/24/1989 (Box 15, Folder 69)
  - Dear Elyakim, 11/24/1989 (Box 15, Folder 70)
  - Dear Ed, 11/24/1989 (Box 15, Folder 71)
  - Dear Will, 12/13/1989 (Box 15, Folder 72)
  - The Suburban exposed the problem: Will we face up to the challenge?, 12/12/1989 (Box 15, Folder 73)
  - Israel and human rights, 12/04/1989 (Box 15, Folder 74)
  - The Jerusalem Post controversy - True & False: How legitimate is the owners' quest for a better, balanced and profitable newspaper?, 01/01/1990 (Box 15, Folder 75)
  - Arab anti-Semitism called threat to Israel, 01/04/1990 (Box 15, Folder 76)
  - Peace not possible: ex-member of PLO, 01/11/1990 (Box 15, Folder 77)
  - Demographic suicide, 01/01/1990 (Box 15, Folder 78)
  - Nobel Peace prizewinners and transfer of Arabs, 01/16/1990 (Box 15, Folder 79)
  - Jewish Agency Committee for transfer of Arabs, 01/20/1990 (Box 15, Folder 80)
  - Our partner for peace (Box 15, Folder 81)
  - Dear Will, 02/13/1990 (Box 15, Folder 82)
  - Postmortem of a failed uprising: The Jerusalem Post in test of time, 02/1990 (Box 15, Folder 83)
  - Answering back to the accusers: Anti-Arab discrimination in Israel?, 03/01/1990 (Box 15, Folder 84)
  - Canada's Israeli friendship ends, 03/21/1990 (Box 15, Folder 85)
  - Dear Mr. Kirshner, 03/06/1990 (Box 15, Folder 86)
  - Dear Stanley, 03/14/1990 (Box 15, Folder 87)
  - Backgrounder: Conrad Black ushers in new Jerusalem Post, 03/15/1990 (Box 15, Folder 88)
  - On whose side are our American Jewish community councils?, 03/01/1990 (Box 15, Folder 89)
  - Dear Dan, 03/08/1990 (Box 15, Folder 90)
  - JINSA - West Bank ideal for 'smart weapons', 04/19/1990 (Box 15, Folder 91)
  - Dear Sol, 04/25/1990 (Box 15, Folder 92)
  - Those damned 'settlements' (Box 15, Folder 93)
  - Those damned 'settlements', 04/1990 (Box 15, Folder 94)
  - Jerusalem think tank study warns against a Palestinian state, 05/04/1990 (Box 15, Folder 95)
  - Full text of Arafat "open fire" order, 05/1990 (Box 15, Folder 96)
  - South Africans can talk to old foes, why not the Israelis?, 05/1990 (Box 15, Folder 97)
  - Israel's territorial imperatives: Col. Irving Kett was sent to Israel in 1974 by the U.S. War College to ..., 05/1990 (Box 15, Folder 98)
  - Bold move into old city was laudable, 05/1990 (Box 15, Folder 99)
  - Dear Stanley, 05/04/1990 (Box 15, Folder 100)
  - Dear Sol, 06/13/1990 (Box 15, Folder 101)
  - Building one's fortune on someone else's misfortune, 06/27/1990 (Box 15, Folder 102)
  - Mandela's "apology" manifested in Jewish self-deception, 06/25/1990 (Box 15, Folder 103)
  - Dear Friends, 07/19/1990 (Box 15, Folder 104)
  - Dear Reader, 08/13/1990 (Box 15, Folder 105)
  - Reader's letters: Historic falsehoods, 09/1990 (Box 15, Folder 106)
  - Jewish groups hit 'smear' of pro-rights fund in Israel, 09/1990 (Box 15, Folder 107)
  - Weekly will offer another voice: Bronfman group launches newsmagazine in Israel, 09/1990 (Box 15, Folder 108)
  - On 13 September 1990 the United Nations postal administration is issuing an antisemitic stamp bearing a Nazi-like caricature of Jews as thieves, 09/04/1990 (Box 15, Folder 109)
  - Peace, security - not politics, 09/1990 (Box 15, Folder 110)